<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Arwen</title>
    <description>An adventure time blog.</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Sat, 24 Mar 2018 10:59:03 +0100</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 24 Mar 2018 10:59:03 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.6.2</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Milford Sound Days 2 and 3</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;We awoke to find the steady downpour the night before had left the surrounding mountains snow capped, but finally the rain had stopped. Nick and I parted ways and I slowly made my way to the Milford Sound. With the weather clearer, but much colder, I was able to fully appreciate all the viewpoints I had skipped the day before. I even got the opportunity to see a Kea, the only alpine parrot in the world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/QrBeGlsl.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Kea!&quot; /&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/ctWbQtkl.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When I finally got to the Milford Sound I hopped in a kayak for a guided paddle and walk of the Milford Track. The kayak portion was much shorter than I would have liked, but the Milford Track was what I was really looking forward. We walked the last 5 km of the 4 day tramp to the Giants Gate Falls. While we were walking the clouds finally cleared and we caught a dark pink, orange sunset over the bay.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/VzQdiwll.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Kayaking in a rainforest&quot; /&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/U9jRYQzl.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Park of the Kayak Hike&quot; /&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/7p3Kb7El.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Giant's Gate&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My final day in Fiordland started at 7 AM with a frozen tent and an early cruise of the Milford Sound. I am extremely thankful that I picked up the comforter because my  sleeping bag would definitely not have been enough in the below freezing temps. The cruise gave me a full view of the fjord I’ve been eyeing for the past few days. Including some dips under waterfalls, we got to see some seals and dolphins playing in front of the boat. I’m glad I held off until the last day for the cruise because despite being incredibly cold, it was the clearest I’ve seen it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/Si83n1bl.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Mountains behind Lake Gunn&quot; /&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/q8Ouwm8l.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Dolphins!&quot; /&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/olwwi1Hl.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Sun shining on the Milford Sound&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Afterwards I headed to Gertrude’s Saddle, one of the most difficult hikes I’ve been on in a while. Fortunately I met a young boy from Switzerland near the bottom of the hike who was also looking for a hiking buddy as this was not a hike I wanted to do alone. It took a little over an hour to make it to Black Lake, and another 45 minutes to Gertrude’s Saddle. The final part of the hike was a combination of smooth rock with steel ropes to hang on to and giant rocks covered in snow. Jumping from boulder to boulder reminded me of the rocks I grew up playing on in the desert as a kid, but much, much colder. At the top of Gertrude Saddle’s we got a clear view all the way to Milford Sound, and I ran into the best friends from Germany from camping.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/ojSQvXcl.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Sample of the hike&quot; /&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/ZAld5g3l.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Black Lake&quot; /&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/XA9F32Nl.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Gertrude's Saddle&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After a tedious hike back down with the girls, which was almost scarier than the way up, I hopped in my car and said goodbye to Milford Sound. I camped on a farm halfway between Te Anau and Queenstown where I got a much needed shower and washing machine.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/WbwYpoOl.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Mirror Lake's Clever Sign&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/articles/2018-03/Milford-Sound-Days-2-and-3</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/articles/2018-03/Milford-Sound-Days-2-and-3</guid>
        
        
        <category>New Zealand</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Milford Sound</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I woke up early and packed my tent in the dark and rain and finished the trip to the Milford Sound. The campsite was first come first serve, so I thought I needed to arrive early, but I’ve learned campsites here don’t fill up like they do in California. Even if they are full, people just find a place to park and nobody seems to care. I’ve heard the drive in is beautiful, but it was so dark and rainy, I could barely see anything. After setting up at a camp about an hour from the Milford Sound, I finished the drive in. The clouds hung on the massive mountains that were covered in trees and waterfalls that rose on either side of the road. The rivers, overloaded with rain water, gushed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/lPnzTWyl.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/X8LA1t8l.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Roadside Waterfall&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The actual Milford Sound was gorgeous as well, although I knew I could only get a small glimpse from where I was on the docks. The rain finally let up around 1, and I ran into for the third time the same traveler from Moreaki Boulders. He was going on a cruise and I was going on a hike, but he said he would camp at the same spot as me. I made my way to Lake Marian, a three hour round trip hike to a lake high in the mountains. It was much more difficult than I thought it would be, the path was hard to follow, steep, and involved climbing over rocks and through the roots of trees. The hike throught the rainforest was well worth it, as the glacial lake was completely secluded and the same beautiful blue I’ve been seeing at all the lakes here. I’m running out of words to describe just how gorgeous New Zealand is.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/bd7zrMsl.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;River beside Lake Marian Track&quot; /&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/J3bkaoKl.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Lake Marian&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After I returned to the campsite it started raining again and wind picked up so we went to a sheltered cooking area where a bunch of campers had gathered to make dinner. Here I got something I’ve been missing this trip. Since I’ve started camping, I’ve only had real conversations with two or three people, and one of those people is Nick who I kept running into. While I like being alone, especially the quiet that allows to enjoy nature, I also love meeting people and hearing their stories. Nick is an organic chemist turned star expert who sailed here from Australia, and was planning to sail to a small island in Asia to start his own star gazing/contemplation business off his boat. I met a Polish couple who planned to run the Milford Track, normally a 4 day Trek, in an estimated 12 hours. Two best friends from Germany told us how their mothers swapped taking care of them every two days when they were growing up. The night was filled with laughter and a colliding of cultures. It’s not that I’ve been lonely, but one of my favorite things about traveling is getting little glimpse of peoples lives from all over the world. It brings out an outgoing side of me that’s normally hidden at home. Perhaps it’s the freedom of knowing that I’ll only be a part of these people’s lives for a day at most, perhaps it’s a magical power only activated by leaving the country.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 21 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/articles/2018-03/The-Milford-Sound</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/articles/2018-03/The-Milford-Sound</guid>
        
        
        <category>New Zealand</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>East and South Coasts</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I spent the day Monday making my way down the South Coast to the Catlins hoping to catch the Southern Lights. After a walk to view where the Waitaki River meets the ocean, I made my way to Moeraki Boulders, smooth, round naturally created boulders on the coast. There were a lot of people there and some sort of event for kids it seemed, but they were still cool to see. I’ve been pretty cold at night so I made a stop to buy a comforter from Salvation Army which ended up costing a whole $12. Afterwards I headed to Tunnel Beach Walkway where arches are formed by the ocean near Dunedin. The high, tan cliffs stood in stark contrast to the light blue sea crashing below. I was able to drop down all the way to the shore, but it was a strenuous hike back up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/ubGevsql.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Reminders to myself&quot; /&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/LmU7Qvdl.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;River meeting ocean&quot; /&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/XnzPhHjl.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Tunnel Beach&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The drive down the coast was beautiful, full of views of the sea, rainforests, and lots of green hills filled with farms. An abundance of sheep farms.
Tawanui campground was far off the beaten path and recommended to me by another traveler at Moreaki Boulders. Right next to a river, there were only two other people at the campsite. The drive into it was through a bright green valley with more cows and sheeps wandering the hills. As much as I love camping, this sort of remote camping can get kind of scary. Mostly it’s just my mind playing tricks on me, but I did keep hearing some sort of large animal making noises all night. It could also just have been my neighbor snoring but who knows.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/D473pKrl.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Moreaki Boulders&quot; /&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/0YhsUtAl.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They say the early bird gets the worm, and I can tell you that I have never gotten the worm and rarely even make it for breakfast. I went to bed with every intention of waking up at 5:30 and making it Te Anau, but my newly acquired comforter made my tent a little too cozy and I ended up not getting up until 8. I still left camp before 9 though so I was pretty happy with that. Knowing I wouldn’t make it to Te Anau anymore, I took the scenic route to Fiordland making a stop at Cathedral Caverns, one of the 30 longest sea caves in the world. I also stopped at Curio Bay hoping to get a glimpse of some sea lions but instead I ended up running into the same traveler from Moreaki Boulders. Afterwards, I hit what I thought would be a straight 4 hour drive to the South Arm campsite.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/bRLhtzol.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Beach at Cathedral Caves&quot; /&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/f4lOsxAl.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Cathedral Caves&quot; /&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/GhxM1OIl.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Curio Bay&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;By the time I reached Fiordland it was dumping rain and I had a 30 mile drive on a dirt road to the secluded campsite. The drive was magical, filled with mountains full of rainforests and roadside waterfalls, but 10 miles from the campsite one of those waterfalls had obliterated the road. I had to turn around and go back to the nearest campsite, an hour and half away. I set up my tent and cooked in the pouring rain, and because of Murphy’s law, the rain stopped as I was sitting in my car eating ramen. I can’t complain about the campsite though, it was free and right next to Lake Monowait. I found most of my stuff has lived up to its waterproofness, although the tent did get pretty wet before I was able to put the rainfly over it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/0LpvaEgl.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Lucky Cows&quot; /&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/f4lOsxAl.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;More from the drive&quot; /&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/InbQdinl.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Cooking in the rain&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 20 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/articles/2018-03/East-and-South-Coasts</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/articles/2018-03/East-and-South-Coasts</guid>
        
        
        <category>New Zealand</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Lake Pukaki and Mt Cook</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I woke up cold and wet, even though I ended up putting the rainfly on in the middle of the night. I have to pack up everything wet and take off without even making breakfast. I’m immediately greeted with beautiful views of Lake Tekapo that I had missed the night before, and the terrible realization I’ve been driving on the wrong side of the road for a while. As I make my way towards Mt Cook/Aoraki Park I pass another beautfiul torquiose lake, Lake Pukaki. Most of the drive up to Mt Cook is next to the massive lake, and I couldn’t stop pulling over for pictures.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/aANdmkwl.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Lake Tekapo&quot; /&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/m88cztBl.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Lake Pukaki and Mt Cook&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When I get to Mt Cook, I head for the Hooker Valley Track and I am not let down. It’s a 3 hour hike out and back to Hooker Lake, and it’s definitely one of the most beautiful hikes I’ve ever taken. The path has 3 swinging bridges over raging rivers that are so high up they make me dizzy. If you know me well, you know I have a pretty big fear of heights.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/SMmuvXil.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Swinging Bridge&quot; /&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/Mme15yVl.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Views from the Hike&quot; /&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/4o31RwFl.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Lunch at Lake Hooker&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After Hooker Valley, I do a quick hike up to a view of Tasman Glacier, the longest glacier in New Zealand. The glacier is very far away, and a giant lake made of the glacier run off sits at the front of it, a lake that didn’t exsist in 1973. When I finish up in Mt Cook, I start heading towards the coast. I picked up a hitchhiker heading my way who plans on spending the next six months in New Zealand and then another 6 months in Australia! I am so excited/jealous of the people who can stay here for so long, I could definitely spend months exploring. The drive to the coast is lined with cow, sheep, and deer farms and reminds me of driving up the 5 in California, but I’m pretty sure the cows here are happier.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/KH2aGWsl.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Finishing the Hike&quot; /&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/m88cztBl.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Tasman Glacier and Lake&quot; /&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/nrp2YrYl.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Drying my Rainfly While I HIke&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I had planned on staying in a small farm town, Duntroon, but when I pulled up to the campsite it was totally empty and I got a weird feeling so I decided to drive another 30 minutes to the coast. I’m glad I did because Waitaki Waters has showers, free laundry and WiFi. It’s also a 5 minute walk from the beach so I got to fall asleep to the sound of crashing waves.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/AsMAGo5l.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Map at Waitaki Waters&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 18 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/articles/2018-03/Mt-Cook</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/articles/2018-03/Mt-Cook</guid>
        
        
        <category>New Zealand</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>New Zealand!</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;One 11 hour flight later, I landed in Christchurch, New Zealand around 5 PM. It feels good to be in a country where I can speak the language and read everything again. My shuttle driver informed me that Christchurch would be crazy the following night for St. Patrick’s Day and I’m tempted to stay another night. However I’ve been city hopping the entire trip and was really looking forward to being able to see the stars again. I stayed in the Jailhouse Hostel, the only hostel I’m planning to stay in this trip. Although Air BnBs have proved the cheapest way to go for a private room(when I’m not camping), hostels are a lot of fun to stay at and a good way to meet people. I shared my room with a girl from San Diego who’s been in New Zealand for two and a half months and is planning to spend the year here. I hit a local pub for some live music, a beer and a big of bowl of potatoes before working on some music and crashing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/gs8elWBl.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;My Room in the Hostel&quot; /&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/ZWuKJnHl.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Preserved Jail Cell&quot; /&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/CyRAXpZl.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The next day I made my way back to the airport after grabbing breakfast at a local coffee co-op with my temporary roommate. I still needed to buy fuel for my stove, some groceries, and a SIM card, pick up the rental car, and turn in my homework before I can leave town. It all takes way longer than I thought it would and it’s almost five by the time I leave Christchurch. I had promised myself I wouldn’t drive at night so I wouldn’t miss out on the gorgeous scenery, and there I was breaking that promise on the first day. Luckily, it didn’t get dark until after eight so I was able to catch some of the rolling green hills and crystal blue water I had seen from the airplane.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/60NIB4Jl.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;The Car!&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My car is a Japanese car and it took me a long time to figure out just how to play the radio, so I drive with one headphone in which is actually legal here. Driving on the left is weird, but it’s not as difficult as I thought it would be. The hardest places to drive I find are parking lots where there’s no lines separating the sides. I do catch myself driving on the wrong side once after a right turn, but I correct myself pretty quickly. By the time I made it Tapeko, it was pitch black so I took the opportunity to practice some night time photography. With no rain in the forecast, I decide to leave my rainfly off and brave the cold to get a full view of the stars tonight.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/ULi5ykul.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;I tried&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For some reason, I’m getting more embarrassed here about my lack of knowledge than I did in China or Japan. In a drive thru at KFC, I asked the cashier for french fries instead of chips… which are the same things. At the gas station I asked the attendant if they didn’t have 1 cent coins here and he looked at me like I was dumb. Maybe now that I’m free to ask whatever questions I want with no language barrier, I’m just destined to make a fool of myself.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 17 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/articles/2018-03/New-Zealand</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/articles/2018-03/New-Zealand</guid>
        
        
        <category>New Zealand</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>12 Hours in China</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I woke up before five to make my nine o’clock flight to China before heading to New Zealand. As we fly into Guangzhou, I can’t believe how many apartment buildings and skyscrapers there are pushing right up to farmland. When I arrived I almost go through immigration for locals and then immigration for domestic flights, until someone finally tells me how to apply for a 24 hour visa. After I’m approved, I stood in line behind what appears to be Guangzhou’s soccer team. Airport security walks through the men asking for signatures and taking pictures. When I make it past customs, there’s rows of people in red jerseys waiting for the team to leave the airport.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It turns out Southern China Airlines provides a free hotel room for travellers with long layovers as well as a tour. I forgo the tour thinking I’ll make it to Canton Tower myself. To my horror, I couldn’t find a currency exchange once I past customs, and nobody seems to understand what I’m asking (because I’m asking in English). I was expecting a Motel 6 kind of deal, but the hotel room is extrememly nice with two beds, a good speaker, and a waterfall showerhead. At this point I’m confused, extremely tired, and penniless. I only have 6 hours left before my shuttle back to the airport, so after chatting with another traveller from Los Angeles, I crash.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/qTlJsb1m.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Hotel Room&quot; /&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/8ndy2Mbm.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Waterfall Shower!&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After my well needed nap I headed out armed with my MasterCard for some exploring and food. Unfortunately nobody accepted MasterCard, and even though I resigned myself to using an ATM, I couldn’t find an ATM that would accept Visa either. Maybe they, but everything is in Chinese and I have no idea what I’m doing. I spent the next hours walking the area around the hotel trying to soak up the little time I had left there. The smog is really bad and when the sun sets, lights from city gets stuck and the man made haze turns a sickening orange. I had heard about smog in China, and suffer from it to a degree in Los Angeles as well, but it’s unreal how thick it is.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/pL4htflm.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;The Smog&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I found a beautiful green park to walk through with a small hill and few ponds filled with lillipads and loud frogs. It’s a nice escape from the honking cars and high rise apartments that line the streets. This is my third city in as many days and life is starting to feel a little a surreal. Just a week and a half ago I was at home cuddled up with my cat and boyfriend and now I’m wandering the streets of a city where I can’t buy any food or speak to anyone. I miss my bed and the comfort of my home, but I’m excited for the upcoming weeks in New Zealand. Although I’m a little bummed I missed seeing the Canton Tower, I learned a valuable lesson about planning.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/kzN7jCpm.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Ma An Shan Park&quot; /&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/2jFxPOEm.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Pretty pond&quot; /&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/A1v4abDm.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Random Statue&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A final note on China: the Internet censorship. I had heard a little about it, like you can’t use Facebook, but it goes way beyond that. There’s no social media at all, google and it’s products like Google Maps are blocked. Accessing websites from outside China was extrememly slow and oftentimes failed. In order to use the free WiFi in the airport I had to scan my passport to get an access account. I found out the government prevents access to some Wikipedia articles and actively takes down content. I did a little research into how Chinese people feel about the censorship and apparently most of them are fine with it and even support it in some cases. My mom points out that the people answering the surveys might be afraid to speak against the government though. If you’re interested in learning more do some googling of your own (if you’re not in China).&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/articles/2018-03/12-Hours-in-China</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/articles/2018-03/12-Hours-in-China</guid>
        
        
        <category>China</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Some Tips for Travelling in Japan</title>
        <description>&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;You will get lost, so give yourself an hour extra where ever you travel. The streets here are small and confusing. Google maps isn’t as precise with directions as it is in the US. The train stations are huge and crowded. Definitely don’t get upset about it, it’s just a part of travelling here.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;The past two times I’ve been to Japan I’ve had a pocket wifi. The first one was provided by the Air BnB my mom and I stayed at and the one I got this past time was from Ninja WiFi. It cost $54 for 7 days, I got a discount by following the link from this site: https://tokyocheapo.com/business/internet/rent-wifi-router-japan/ .&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Stand on the right on escalators, walk on the left. It will be very obvious if you’re standing on the wrong side.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Public restrooms are everywhere, it’s a deam come true for a frequent peer like myself.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Be quiet on the trains. In Los Angeles, it’s not unusual to have people playing music off their phones or speakers, talking and laughing loudly, or generally being annoying. That’s not okay here. If you’re going to talk, talk quietly, do your best not to disturb other people. Bring a book to read and headphones.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Don’t push people. Learn how to say excuse me (sumimasen) and sorry (gomenisai).&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Don’t cross or spread your legs. The trains can get really crowded, and crossing or spreading your legs takes up space.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;The past two times I’ve used a card called “PASMO”. I’ve been able to use it on every line/subway I’ve gotten onto in Tokyo, as well as Kyoto and Osaka. I’ve even used it on the buses in Kyoto. It’s a 500 yen deposit, and then you can fill it up at any train station with as much money as you like. I don’t know anything about the other passes out there, but I’ve been really pleased with this one.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;DO NOT wear your shoes in houses. EVER. Not even for a second, not even to grab something you forgot, never. Just don’t.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Showering in Japan is one of my favorite things. You take a full shower before soaking in the tub, and then share the water with your family/friends you’re sharing a room with. I know if sounds weird, but a nice soak at the end of a full day of adventures is a great way to reenergize.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/Apcmp6Sm.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;My Family's Bathtub&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Make sure your hair is dry before you leave the house unless you want a bunch of obaachans telling you you’ll get sick.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;It’s improper to show your bra straps or bare shoulders. Bra strap slips can be kind of hard to avoid, so just try to pay attention. If people start asking if you’re cold it’s probably because a lot of your shoulders/chest is showing.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;You can get hot drinks from the vending machines! Cold ones are blue below, hot ones are red, they also say if they’re hot/cold if you can read hiragana.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;People here don’t walk and eat. If you buy some food, step to the side and finish it.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;On that note, trash cans are super hard to come across. Japan has a complicated system for sorting their trash, so if you do find a trash can, make sure you put it in right the spot. Don’t be a litterbug, just carry your trash with you.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;If you visit a shrine follow their rules about shoes and photos even if nobody is watching. It’s a privilege to see this places, treat them with respect.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;If you have no idea how to do something just watch the locals, they might even approach you to help if you’re looking super lost.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/articles/2018-03/0-Some-Tips-for-Japan</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/articles/2018-03/0-Some-Tips-for-Japan</guid>
        
        
        <category>Japan</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A Night in Osaka</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;After spending some time in an internet cafe, Miranda and I headed to Osaka where we will meet Miranda’s Mom and sister. If I did this again, I’d definitely stay in Osaka and travel to Kyoto for day trips. Changing Air BnBs and hostels like this was not ideal. For the most part we hang out in the large train station Umeda. It might sound boring, but the stations here are more like ten story malls and this one even has a large Ferris Wheel on top. I am excited for Miranda to have her family in one place, but it means our time together is coming to an end. Although we’ve seen each other every year for the past 11 years, saying goodbye still makes me cry. Last year we both went through some rough times and sometimes a phone call just isn’t enough. Our time together is always a highlight of my year, but sometimes I catch myself letting the time slip through my fingers, forgetting about the 51 other weeks of the year when all I have is her voice.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/depBlyVm.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Ferris Wheel on top of Train Station&quot; /&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/3iFpcGUm.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Whale Inside of Train Station&quot; /&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/33IIbdmm.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Miranda's Family and I&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After I left her and her family I wandered the bar lined streets of Osaka, soaking up my last hours in Japan. In a karoake bar I met two waitresses from China and a Japanese business man with impressive English and they taught me how to say thank in Chinese for my layover the following day. In another I find a band playing live jazz. The pianist recently moved from Los Angeles, just 20 minutes from where I live now. It’s such a strange, small world we live in.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/wEk2RY0m.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;My Hotel Room&quot; /&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/mBo72slm.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Karaoke Bar in Osaka&quot; /&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/fIj2soNm.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Live Music in Karaoke&quot; /&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/lIFQhSGm.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Street Art in Osaka&quot; /&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 14 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/articles/2018-03/A-Night-in-Osaka</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/articles/2018-03/A-Night-in-Osaka</guid>
        
        
        <category>Japan</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A Day in Kyoto</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;After talking with Mairead, we realize that I really only have one full day in Kyoto before I need to make my way to Osaka to catch my flight Thursday morning. Miranda will be staying for another week and a half with her family for Mairead’s graduation, but she agrees to wake up early with me for a full day of exploring in Japan’s old capital. WIth a list of places to visit from Mairead, Kyoto is our oyster for the day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/I6XEiM4m.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Delicious Bakery we Found by the Air BnB&quot; /&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/xt5Hs6nm.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Miranda Brushing up on herJapanese on the Train&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We started at Fushimi Inari Shrine, which I soon find out has been voted Japan’s most popular site for foreign tourists for several years in a row. I recognize this place from pictures my friends have posted from their visits to Japan, but I didn’t realize it would be so busy. I put in my headphones to drown out the crowds, and Miranda and I wander. While Miranda and I watch some sort of religious dancing with fans and bells, it hits me that this is really my first time travelling without my family or the tour guide from our school trip. Without someone there to translate and explain customs, I have no idea what’s going on. I feel the loss of my Grandma heavily there, surrounded by other foreigners, wishing more than anything in the world that she could’ve shown me Japan through her eyes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/H1ybWxzm.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Toriis at Fushimi Inari&quot; /&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/IJpw2B1m.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Inari's Messenger the Fox&quot; /&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/N7xKQBIm.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;More Toriis&quot; /&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/OBztdEEm.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Cat and Toriis&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As overcrowded as it was, Miranda and I are able to find some quiet moments off the most travelled paths. A trail to the summit is lined with bamboo and warnings about boars. Sidewalks lined with larger Toriis and men restoring the orange paint on them leads to a collection of shrines and a cat. After some more festival food, we make our way to Heian Shrine in another part of Kyoto. The shrine has gardens filled with cherry blossom trees, but we are a couple of weeks too early and the trees a bare. Afterwards, we started walking north and found Shoren-in Monzeki and Chion-in. The grounds are gorgeous, impressive, and ancient. After a long day of walking, we decided head to another Sento, this one with a variety of different baths to get in.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/7LJgJ8Dm.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;View From Chion-in&quot; /&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/L4QOJI5m.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Mirand Letting me Practice Picture Taking&quot; /&gt;  &lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/Se1CPmLm.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 13 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/articles/2018-03/A-Day-In-Kyoto</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/articles/2018-03/A-Day-In-Kyoto</guid>
        
        
        <category>Japan</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Tokyo's Tourist Central and the Shinkansen</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Asakusa was the most touristy and busy place we’ve been to yet. Senso-ji, known for it’s large red hanging lanterns, is the oldest temple in Tokyo. The streets are lined wtih shops where you can buy souvenirs, candies, and things for the shrines. There is a steady stream of people trekking to the main shrine, but unlike in the United States I don’t mind the crowds very much. People are more mindful of personal space here and don’t push you out of the way to get to way they’re going like in Los Angeles.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/AbxRaSym.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Asakusa&quot; /&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/zCloioVm.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Cool Satue of Kabuki Actor in Asakusa&quot; /&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/2U2WSJ4m.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Burning Incense&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After some festival food, Miranda I went to a sento. Recommended to us by my Lonely Planet tour book, we were the only foreigners there. This was the first place I’ve really noticed people staring at us. Despite forgetting our towels having to do a dripping wet walk of shame to the lockers, we left feeling relaxed. Even though the crowds here aren’t so bad, soaking in the baths gave us so much needed refreshment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/rvp2Qcum.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Miranda Loving Candy Coated Bananas&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After we bought our tickets for the Shinkansen we met with my family for a final dinner at a place called NINJA Akasaka. They had a vegan set that consisted of a lot of tomatoes and some more traditional and international dishes for everyone else. It was definitely a tourist trap, but we still had fun. They fully committed to the ninja theme and even gave us an impressive magic show at the end of our dinner.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/kZ8yyH9m.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Ninja Sushi&quot; /&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/vUUG0Jwm.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Cheesecake Frog&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Leaving Tokyo is bittersweet. While I’m excited for the rest of my trip, I also don’t know when I’ll see my family again. In the past there’s been an assurance that we’ll see each other again soon because my cousin’s were constantly visiting America to see their grandparents. Now that my great uncle has moved back to Japan, we no longer know when we’ll be able to meet again. Will it be 5 years? 10? Under what circumstances? As much as I want to return to Japan every other year, it’s just not something I can commit to. While my family will always have a place to stay in Los Angeles, it’s not any easier for them to come to the United States. As Miranda and I make our way to Tokyo Station and the Shinkansen, I can’t help but feel like I’m leaving a little part of myself in Tokyo. How can a place I’ve never lived feel so much like home?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/l9EIvN6m.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;My Cousin Juri, a friend, Miranda and I&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It took us around 3 hours to make it to Kyoto, and about and hour and a half to find our Air BnB. Our taxi driver, unable to understand the Google Map I kept showing him, pulled over twice to ask for help from some younger people then dropped us a 15 minute walk from the Air BnB. After we met up with Miranda’s sister, Mairead, we went in to the wrong building and were very close to ringing the doorbell of someone’s apartment when we realized we had the wrong address. Thankfully we weren’t very far off, and the happy sisters could celebrate their reunion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/atLBWnAm.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Our Air BnB in Kyoto&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/articles/2018-03/Tourist-Central-and-the-Shinkansen</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/articles/2018-03/Tourist-Central-and-the-Shinkansen</guid>
        
        
        <category>Japan</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
