<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Arwen</title>
    <description>An adventure time blog.</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Sat, 10 Mar 2018 17:32:59 +0100</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Mar 2018 17:32:59 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.6.2</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Harajuku, the Imperial Palace, and Crepes</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Harajuku has one of my favorite foods in the world: cheesecake, ice cream, whipped cream, and fruit stuffed crepes wrapped into a cone. Normally I don’t like sweets, but there’s something about this sugar trap that leaves me craving it long after I leave Japan. After beelining it to Takeshita-Dori for my weakness, Miranda and I wandered through the brightly colored stores blasting JPop. We stopped in a Purikura to take some awkward pictures and of course visited a cat cafe. Tucked discreetly behind Harajuku, Meiji Shrine lies under a blanket of green. It’s a jarring experience going from the loud, flashing lights of Harajuku to the Meiji grounds. The temperature drops below the trees and large Toriis line the pathways. We didn’t have much time to explore though so we promise to come back.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Still in Harajuku, we meet with one of my cousins that I haven’t seen since I was 14 and she was 7. Juuna, my mom’s cousin’s kid, wants to go to college in Los Angeles and is obviously serious about her English studies. Even though it’s been 10 years since we saw each other (and she doesn’t even remember that!), there’s a level of comfort I always feel with my family here. It doesn’t seem to matter how little I see them, or if we’ve never even met before, they’re always so nice and interested. I hope one day they will visit Los Angeles so I can return the kindness. Afterwards, Miranda and I head to dinner for what feels like a 20 course meal&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 10 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/articles/2018-03/Harajuku-and-the-Imperial-Palace</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/articles/2018-03/Harajuku-and-the-Imperial-Palace</guid>
        
        
        <category>Japan</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Tama and Family</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;One uber, two bus rides and and an 11 hour flight later, I finally made it to my family’s place in Tama. I’ll be staying in my Great Uncle’s apartment, just a floor away from his daughter and grandchildren. Uncle Mori moved back to Japan last year after living in the United States for 40 years. He tells me that this is not the Japan he once lived in, technology so embedded in everything he struggles just with the washing machine. I’m excited to see him and spend time with him, I’ve always felt like he and my great aunt (my grandma’s sister) were like another pair of grandparents. After my grandma passed, Aunt Kumiko kept me in touch with my Japanese side. Their grandchildren would come to visit and they became like cousins to me. There was always a language barrier to overcome but we bonded over Powderpuff Girls and communicated through hand signals. As we grew older, I was able to take them with me around Los Angeles.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With them, I feel comfortable; I stayed in this apartment the last time I was here with my Mom and my “Aunt” Keiko and Uncle Mori are both fluent in English. When I wander outside of the apartment though, I feel out of place. At 5’7”, I’m taller than most girls here and a lot of the guys. My family lives in a suburb of Tokyo and I haven’t seen a single foreigner anywhere near here. As I leave my Uncle’s apartment I hear a little asking her mom who I am. I keep forgetting to speak Japanese, and respond in English or give up on a sentence halfway through. There was a time when I seriously considered moving to Japan to teach Japanese, but after spending a week here with my mother I felt too rude and restricted to ever move here.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/DE0HOV3m.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Korochan&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today it rained all day, something that Los Angeles has been lacking this winter. I split the day with spending time with my cousin and uncle, and trying to finish homework before Miranda arrives. I got lost trying to find a cafe in Shibuya called Caffice . It’s filled with other people working, and I even see a guy with a Randy’s Donuts sticker on his laptop. The wifi is fast, but the coffee is expensive ($8 for a mocha!). Although I liked the workspace vibe, I’d probably find a cheaper place to work if I planned on staying more than a couple of hours.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/Rnwpy2qm.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;KoheiAndMori&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Miranda’s bus arrived 40 minutes late most likely due to rain. My uncle, always accommadating, braved the cold and waited with me. After 30 hours of travelling, Miranda is ready to call it night and my jetlag catches up to me as well.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 08 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/articles/2018-03/Tama-and-Family</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/articles/2018-03/Tama-and-Family</guid>
        
        
        <category>Japan</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A Packing List, Everything Plus the Kitchen Sink</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The past few weeks have been a blur of running errands, making never ending lists, and trying to focus on school work. Preparing for this trip has been a little crazy as I’ve tried to balance having to carry a full set of camping gear along with clothes to keep me cozy through a chilly Japanese spring, fall in New Zealand, and a sunny Hawaii in April. In case anybody’s curious here’s everything I brought along (I am well aware I am bringning too many clothes).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/CevJ8LGl.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Packing&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;clothes&quot;&gt;Clothes&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Sandals, flats, and hiking boots&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;(6) T-shirts&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;(4) Long sleeves&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;(4) Tank tops&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;(2) Spaghetti straps&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;(3) Work out shirts&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;(2) Top and bottom thermals&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;(2) Leggings&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;(2) Jeans&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Tights&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Jean, work out, and pajama shorts&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Flannel&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Hoodie&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Fleece jacket&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Rain jacket&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Dress&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;(2) Gloves&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;(2) Headbands&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Beanie&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Scarf&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;camping-gear&quot;&gt;Camping Gear&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Tent&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Sleeping bag and pad&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Multitool and pocket knmife&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Jet boiler&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Pan&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Folding spatula&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Spork&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Insect net&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Sink&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Biodegradable soap&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Sponge&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Clips and rope (for laundry)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;electronics&quot;&gt;Electronics&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Headlamp&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Lantern&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Reading light&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Extra batteries&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;(2) External batteries&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Car charger&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;AUX cord&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Laptop and laptop charger&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Camera, extra batteries, and chargers&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Headphones and bluetooth headphones&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Fujifilm camera&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Attachable phone lens’&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;miscellaneous&quot;&gt;Miscellaneous&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Umbrella&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Reusable Bag&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Small purse&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Sunglasses&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Teddy bear&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Water bottle&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;toiletries&quot;&gt;Toiletries&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Toiletries are a pretty personal choice, so I don’t feel like anyone would gain anything from me posting mine&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 06 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/articles/2018-03/a-packing-list</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/articles/2018-03/a-packing-list</guid>
        
        
        <category>Packing</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
