<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Arwen</title>
    <description>An adventure time blog.</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Sun, 18 Mar 2018 12:39:21 +0100</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 18 Mar 2018 12:39:21 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.6.2</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Lake Pukaki and Mt Cook</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I woke up cold and wet, even though I ended up putting the rainfly on in the middle of the night. I have to pack up everything wet and take off without even making breakfast. I’m immediately greeted with beautiful views of Lake Tekapo that I had missed the night before, and the terrible realization I’ve been driving on the wrong side of the road for a while. As I make my way towards Mt Cook/Aoraki Park I pass another beautfiul torquiose lake, Lake Pukaki. Most of the drive up to Mt Cook is next to the massive lake, and I couldn’t stop pulling over for pictures.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/aANdmkwm.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Lake Tekapo&quot; /&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/m88cztBm.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Lake Pukaki and Mt Cook&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When I get to Mt Cook, I head for the Hooker Valley Track and I am not let down. It’s a 3 hour hike out and back to Hooker Lake, and it’s definitely one of the most beautiful hikes I’ve ever taken. The path has 3 swinging bridges over raging rivers that are so high up they make me dizzy. If you know me well, you know I have a pretty big fear of heights.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/SMmuvXim.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Swinging Bridge&quot; /&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/Mme15yVm.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Views from the Hike&quot; /&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/4o31RwFm.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Lunch at Lake Hooker&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After Hooker Valley, I do a quick hike up to a view of Tasman Glacier, the longest glacier in New Zealand. The glacier is very far away, and a giant lake made of the glacier run off sits at the front of it, a lake that didn’t exsist in 1973. When I finish up in Mt Cook, I start heading towards the coast. I picked up a hitchhiker heading my way who plans on spending the next six months in New Zealand and then another 6 months in Australia! I am so excited/jealous of the people who can stay here for so long, I could definitely spend months exploring. The drive to the coast is lined with cow, sheep, and deer farms and reminds me of driving up the 5 in California, but I’m pretty sure the cows here are happier.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/KH2aGWsm.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Finishing the Hike&quot; /&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/m88cztBm.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Tasman Glacier and Lake&quot; /&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/nrp2YrYm.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Drying my Rainfly While I HIke&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I had planned on staying in a small farm town, Duntroon, but when I pulled up to the campsite it was totally empty and I got a weird feeling so I decided to drive another 30 minutes to the coast. I’m glad I did because Waitaki Waters has showers, free laundry and WiFi. It’s also a 5 minute walk from the beach so I got to fall asleep to the sound of crashing waves.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/AsMAGo5m.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Map at Waitaki Waters&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 18 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/articles/2018-03/Mt-Cook</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/articles/2018-03/Mt-Cook</guid>
        
        
        <category>New Zealand</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>New Zealand!</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;One 11 hour flight later, I landed in Christchurch, New Zealand around 5 PM. It feels good to be in a country where I can speak the language and read everything again. My shuttle driver informed me that Christchurch would be crazy the following night for St. Patrick’s Day and I’m tempted to stay another night. However I’ve been city hopping the entire trip and was really looking forward to being able to see the stars again. I stayed in the Jailhouse Hostel, the only hostel I’m planning to stay in this trip. Although Air BnBs have proved the cheapest way to go for a private room(when I’m not camping), hostels are a lot of fun to stay at and a good way to meet people. I shared my room with a girl from San Diego who’s been in New Zealand for two and a half months and is planning to spend the year here. I hit a local pub for some live music, a beer and a big of bowl of potatoes before working on some music and crashing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/gs8elWBm.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;My Room in the Hostel&quot; /&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/ZWuKJnHm.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Preserved Jail Cell&quot; /&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/CyRAXpZm.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The next day I made my way back to the airport after grabbing breakfast at a local coffee co-op with my temporary roommate. I still needed to buy fuel for my stove, some groceries, and a SIM card, pick up the rental car, and turn in my homework before I can leave town. It all takes way longer than I thought it would and it’s almost five by the time I leave Christchurch. I had promised myself I wouldn’t drive at night so I wouldn’t miss out on the gorgeous scenery, and there I was breaking that promise on the first day. Luckily, it didn’t get dark until after eight so I was able to catch some of the rolling green hills and crystal blue water I had seen from the airplane.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/60NIB4Jm.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;The Car!&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My car is a Japanese car and it took me a long time to figure out just how to play the radio, so I drive with one headphone in which is actually legal here. Driving on the left is weird, but it’s not as difficult as I thought it would be. The hardest places to drive I find are parking lots where there’s no lines separating the sides. I do catch myself driving on the wrong side once after a right turn, but I correct myself pretty quickly. By the time I made it Tapeko, it was pitch black so I took the opportunity to practice some night time photography. With no rain in the forecast, I decide to leave my rainfly off and brave the cold to get a full view of the stars tonight.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/ULi5ykum.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;I tried&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For some reason, I’m getting more embarrassed here about my lack of knowledge than I did in China or Japan. In a drive thru at KFC, I asked the cashier for french fries instead of chips… which are the same things. At the gas station I asked the attendant if they didn’t have 1 cent coins here and he looked at me like I was dumb. Maybe now that I’m free to ask whatever questions I want with no language barrier, I’m just destined to make a fool of myself.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 17 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/articles/2018-03/New-Zealand</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/articles/2018-03/New-Zealand</guid>
        
        
        <category>New Zealand</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>12 Hours in China</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I woke up before five to make my nine o’clock flight to China before heading to New Zealand. As we fly into Guangzhou, I can’t believe how many apartment buildings and skyscrapers there are pushing right up to farmland. When I arrived I almost go through immigration for locals and then immigration for domestic flights, until someone finally tells me how to apply for a 24 hour visa. After I’m approved, I stood in line behind what appears to be Guangzhou’s soccer team. Airport security walks through the men asking for signatures and taking pictures. When I make it past customs, there’s rows of people in red jerseys waiting for the team to leave the airport.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It turns out Southern China Airlines provides a free hotel room for travellers with long layovers as well as a tour. I forgo the tour thinking I’ll make it to Canton Tower myself. To my horror, I couldn’t find a currency exchange once I past customs, and nobody seems to understand what I’m asking (because I’m asking in English). I was expecting a Motel 6 kind of deal, but the hotel room is extrememly nice with two beds, a good speaker, and a waterfall showerhead. At this point I’m confused, extremely tired, and penniless. I only have 6 hours left before my shuttle back to the airport, so after chatting with another traveller from Los Angeles, I crash.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/qTlJsb1m.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Hotel Room&quot; /&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/8ndy2Mbm.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Waterfall Shower!&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After my well needed nap I headed out armed with my MasterCard for some exploring and food. Unfortunately nobody accepted MasterCard, and even though I resigned myself to using an ATM, I couldn’t find an ATM that would accept Visa either. Maybe they, but everything is in Chinese and I have no idea what I’m doing. I spent the next hours walking the area around the hotel trying to soak up the little time I had left there. The smog is really bad and when the sun sets, lights from city gets stuck and the man made haze turns a sickening orange. I had heard about smog in China, and suffer from it to a degree in Los Angeles as well, but it’s unreal how thick it is.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/pL4htflm.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;The Smog&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I found a beautiful green park to walk through with a small hill and few ponds filled with lillipads and loud frogs. It’s a nice escape from the honking cars and high rise apartments that line the streets. This is my third city in as many days and life is starting to feel a little a surreal. Just a week and a half ago I was at home cuddled up with my cat and boyfriend and now I’m wandering the streets of a city where I can’t buy any food or speak to anyone. I miss my bed and the comfort of my home, but I’m excited for the upcoming weeks in New Zealand. Although I’m a little bummed I missed seeing the Canton Tower, I learned a valuable lesson about planning.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/kzN7jCpm.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Ma An Shan Park&quot; /&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/2jFxPOEm.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Pretty pond&quot; /&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/A1v4abDm.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Random Statue&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A final note on China: the Internet censorship. I had heard a little about it, like you can’t use Facebook, but it goes way beyond that. There’s no social media at all, google and it’s products like Google Maps are blocked. Accessing websites from outside China was extrememly slow and oftentimes failed. In order to use the free WiFi in the airport I had to scan my passport to get an access account. I found out the government prevents access to some Wikipedia articles and actively takes down content. I did a little research into how Chinese people feel about the censorship and apparently most of them are fine with it and even support it in some cases. My mom points out that the people answering the surveys might be afraid to speak against the government though. If you’re interested in learning more do some googling of your own (if you’re not in China).&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/articles/2018-03/12-Hours-in-China</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/articles/2018-03/12-Hours-in-China</guid>
        
        
        <category>China</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Some Tips for Travelling in Japan</title>
        <description>&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;You will get lost, so give yourself an hour extra where ever you travel. The streets here are small and confusing. Google maps isn’t as precise with directions as it is in the US. The train stations are huge and crowded. Definitely don’t get upset about it, it’s just a part of travelling here.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;The past two times I’ve been to Japan I’ve had a pocket wifi. The first one was provided by the Air BnB my mom and I stayed at and the one I got this past time was from Ninja WiFi. It cost $54 for 7 days, I got a discount by following the link from this site: https://tokyocheapo.com/business/internet/rent-wifi-router-japan/ .&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Stand on the right on escalators, walk on the left. It will be very obvious if you’re standing on the wrong side.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Public restrooms are everywhere, it’s a deam come true for a frequent peer like myself.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Be quiet on the trains. In Los Angeles, it’s not unusual to have people playing music off their phones or speakers, talking and laughing loudly, or generally being annoying. That’s not okay here. If you’re going to talk, talk quietly, do your best not to disturb other people. Bring a book to read and headphones.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Don’t push people. Learn how to say excuse me (sumimasen) and sorry (gomenisai).&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Don’t cross or spread your legs. The trains can get really crowded, and crossing or spreading your legs takes up space.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;The past two times I’ve used a card called “PASMO”. I’ve been able to use it on every line/subway I’ve gotten onto in Tokyo, as well as Kyoto and Osaka. I’ve even used it on the buses in Kyoto. It’s a 500 yen deposit, and then you can fill it up at any train station with as much money as you like. I don’t know anything about the other passes out there, but I’ve been really pleased with this one.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;DO NOT wear your shoes in houses. EVER. Not even for a second, not even to grab something you forgot, never. Just don’t.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Showering in Japan is one of my favorite things. You take a full shower before soaking in the tub, and then share the water with your family/friends you’re sharing a room with. I know if sounds weird, but a nice soak at the end of a full day of adventures is a great way to reenergize.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/Apcmp6Sm.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;My Family's Bathtub&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Make sure your hair is dry before you leave the house unless you want a bunch of obaachans telling you you’ll get sick.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;It’s improper to show your bra straps or bare shoulders. Bra strap slips can be kind of hard to avoid, so just try to pay attention. If people start asking if you’re cold it’s probably because a lot of your shoulders/chest is showing.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;You can get hot drinks from the vending machines! Cold ones are blue below, hot ones are red, they also say if they’re hot/cold if you can read hiragana.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;People here don’t walk and eat. If you buy some food, step to the side and finish it.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;On that note, trash cans are super hard to come across. Japan has a complicated system for sorting their trash, so if you do find a trash can, make sure you put it in right the spot. Don’t be a litterbug, just carry your trash with you.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;If you visit a shrine follow their rules about shoes and photos even if nobody is watching. It’s a privilege to see this places, treat them with respect.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;If you have no idea how to do something just watch the locals, they might even approach you to help if you’re looking super lost.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/articles/2018-03/0-Some-Tips-for-Japan</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/articles/2018-03/0-Some-Tips-for-Japan</guid>
        
        
        <category>Japan</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A Night in Osaka</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;After spending some time in an internet cafe, Miranda and I headed to Osaka where we will meet Miranda’s Mom and sister. If I did this again, I’d definitely stay in Osaka and travel to Kyoto for day trips. Changing Air BnBs and hostels like this was not ideal. For the most part we hang out in the large train station Umeda. It might sound boring, but the stations here are more like ten story malls and this one even has a large Ferris Wheel on top. I am excited for Miranda to have her family in one place, but it means our time together is coming to an end. Although we’ve seen each other every year for the past 11 years, saying goodbye still makes me cry. Last year we both went through some rough times and sometimes a phone call just isn’t enough. Our time together is always a highlight of my year, but sometimes I catch myself letting the time slip through my fingers, forgetting about the 51 other weeks of the year when all I have is her voice.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/depBlyVm.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Ferris Wheel on top of Train Station&quot; /&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/3iFpcGUm.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Whale Inside of Train Station&quot; /&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/33IIbdmm.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Miranda's Family and I&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After I left her and her family I wandered the bar lined streets of Osaka, soaking up my last hours in Japan. In a karoake bar I met two waitresses from China and a Japanese business man with impressive English and they taught me how to say thank in Chinese for my layover the following day. In another I find a band playing live jazz. The pianist recently moved from Los Angeles, just 20 minutes from where I live now. It’s such a strange, small world we live in.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/wEk2RY0m.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;My Hotel Room&quot; /&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/mBo72slm.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Karaoke Bar in Osaka&quot; /&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/fIj2soNm.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Live Music in Karaoke&quot; /&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/lIFQhSGm.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Street Art in Osaka&quot; /&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 14 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/articles/2018-03/A-Night-in-Osaka</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/articles/2018-03/A-Night-in-Osaka</guid>
        
        
        <category>Japan</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A Day in Kyoto</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;After talking with Mairead, we realize that I really only have one full day in Kyoto before I need to make my way to Osaka to catch my flight Thursday morning. Miranda will be staying for another week and a half with her family for Mairead’s graduation, but she agrees to wake up early with me for a full day of exploring in Japan’s old capital. WIth a list of places to visit from Mairead, Kyoto is our oyster for the day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/I6XEiM4m.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Delicious Bakery we Found by the Air BnB&quot; /&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/xt5Hs6nm.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Miranda Brushing up on herJapanese on the Train&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We started at Fushimi Inari Shrine, which I soon find out has been voted Japan’s most popular site for foreign tourists for several years in a row. I recognize this place from pictures my friends have posted from their visits to Japan, but I didn’t realize it would be so busy. I put in my headphones to drown out the crowds, and Miranda and I wander. While Miranda and I watch some sort of religious dancing with fans and bells, it hits me that this is really my first time travelling without my family or the tour guide from our school trip. Without someone there to translate and explain customs, I have no idea what’s going on. I feel the loss of my Grandma heavily there, surrounded by other foreigners, wishing more than anything in the world that she could’ve shown me Japan through her eyes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/H1ybWxzm.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Toriis at Fushimi Inari&quot; /&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/IJpw2B1m.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Inari's Messenger the Fox&quot; /&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/N7xKQBIm.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;More Toriis&quot; /&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/OBztdEEm.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Cat and Toriis&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As overcrowded as it was, Miranda and I are able to find some quiet moments off the most travelled paths. A trail to the summit is lined with bamboo and warnings about boars. Sidewalks lined with larger Toriis and men restoring the orange paint on them leads to a collection of shrines and a cat. After some more festival food, we make our way to Heian Shrine in another part of Kyoto. The shrine has gardens filled with cherry blossom trees, but we are a couple of weeks too early and the trees a bare. Afterwards, we started walking north and found Shoren-in Monzeki and Chion-in. The grounds are gorgeous, impressive, and ancient. After a long day of walking, we decided head to another Sento, this one with a variety of different baths to get in.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/7LJgJ8Dm.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;View From Chion-in&quot; /&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/L4QOJI5m.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Mirand Letting me Practice Picture Taking&quot; /&gt;  &lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/Se1CPmLm.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 13 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/articles/2018-03/A-Day-In-Kyoto</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/articles/2018-03/A-Day-In-Kyoto</guid>
        
        
        <category>Japan</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Tokyo's Tourist Central and the Shinkansen</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Asakusa was the most touristy and busy place we’ve been to yet. Senso-ji, known for it’s large red hanging lanterns, is the oldest temple in Tokyo. The streets are lined wtih shops where you can buy souvenirs, candies, and things for the shrines. There is a steady stream of people trekking to the main shrine, but unlike in the United States I don’t mind the crowds very much. People are more mindful of personal space here and don’t push you out of the way to get to way they’re going like in Los Angeles.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/AbxRaSym.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Asakusa&quot; /&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/zCloioVm.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Cool Satue of Kabuki Actor in Asakusa&quot; /&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/2U2WSJ4m.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Burning Incense&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After some festival food, Miranda I went to a sento. Recommended to us by my Lonely Planet tour book, we were the only foreigners there. This was the first place I’ve really noticed people staring at us. Despite forgetting our towels having to do a dripping wet walk of shame to the lockers, we left feeling relaxed. Even though the crowds here aren’t so bad, soaking in the baths gave us so much needed refreshment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/rvp2Qcum.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Miranda Loving Candy Coated Bananas&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After we bought our tickets for the Shinkansen we met with my family for a final dinner at a place called NINJA Akasaka. They had a vegan set that consisted of a lot of tomatoes and some more traditional and international dishes for everyone else. It was definitely a tourist trap, but we still had fun. They fully committed to the ninja theme and even gave us an impressive magic show at the end of our dinner.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/kZ8yyH9m.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Ninja Sushi&quot; /&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/vUUG0Jwm.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Cheesecake Frog&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Leaving Tokyo is bittersweet. While I’m excited for the rest of my trip, I also don’t know when I’ll see my family again. In the past there’s been an assurance that we’ll see each other again soon because my cousin’s were constantly visiting America to see their grandparents. Now that my great uncle has moved back to Japan, we no longer know when we’ll be able to meet again. Will it be 5 years? 10? Under what circumstances? As much as I want to return to Japan every other year, it’s just not something I can commit to. While my family will always have a place to stay in Los Angeles, it’s not any easier for them to come to the United States. As Miranda and I make our way to Tokyo Station and the Shinkansen, I can’t help but feel like I’m leaving a little part of myself in Tokyo. How can a place I’ve never lived feel so much like home?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/l9EIvN6m.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;My Cousin Juri, a friend, Miranda and I&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It took us around 3 hours to make it to Kyoto, and about and hour and a half to find our Air BnB. Our taxi driver, unable to understand the Google Map I kept showing him, pulled over twice to ask for help from some younger people then dropped us a 15 minute walk from the Air BnB. After we met up with Miranda’s sister, Mairead, we went in to the wrong building and were very close to ringing the doorbell of someone’s apartment when we realized we had the wrong address. Thankfully we weren’t very far off, and the happy sisters could celebrate their reunion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/atLBWnAm.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Our Air BnB in Kyoto&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/articles/2018-03/Tourist-Central-and-the-Shinkansen</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/articles/2018-03/Tourist-Central-and-the-Shinkansen</guid>
        
        
        <category>Japan</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Harajuku, the Imperial Palace, and Crepes</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Harajuku has one of my favorite foods in the world: cheesecake, ice cream, whipped cream, and fruit stuffed crepes wrapped into a cone. Normally I don’t like sweets, but there’s something about this sugar trap that leaves me craving it long after I leave Japan. After beelining it to Takeshita-Dori for my weakness, Miranda and I wandered through the brightly colored stores blasting JPop. We stopped in a Purikura to take some awkward pictures and of course visited a cat cafe. Tucked discreetly behind Harajuku, Meiji Shrine lies under a blanket of green. It’s a jarring experience going from the loud, flashing lights of Harajuku to the Meiji grounds. The temperature drops below the trees and large Toriis line the pathways. We didn’t have much time to explore though so we promise to come back.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/75uFT3Qm.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Harajuku Cat&quot; /&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/F8CxH5km.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Meiji Shrine&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Still in Harajuku, we met with one of my cousins that I haven’t seen since I was 14 and she was 7. Juuna, my mom’s cousin’s daughter, wants to go to college in Los Angeles and is obviously serious about her English studies. Even though it’s been 10 years since we saw each other (and she doesn’t even remember that!), there’s a level of comfort I always feel with my family here. It doesn’t seem to matter how little I see them, or if we’ve never even met before, they’re always so nice and interested. I hope one day they will visit Los Angeles so I can return their hospitality. Afterwards, Miranda and I head to dinner for what feels like a 20 course meal of tempura with Uncle Mori and Aunt Keiko. Completely stuffed, Miranda fell asleep on the couch while I desparetly try to finish my homework.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;By Saturday, the rain had finally stopped. We woke up early to cook my family an American breakfast as a thank you for their kindness. After a little bit of homework, we made our way to the Imperial Palace. The first time I visited Japan, I came with my college and spent my first two weeks traveling with them. I know I visited the imperial palace with them, but I was young and the time I spent with my school is a blur of temples, shrines, and tours.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/KaT7ULjm.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Dinner with Family&quot; /&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/hXDKN0wm.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Pink Flowers on a Tree&quot; /&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/A8k6C16m.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Imperal Palace Garden&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A short walk from the station, the ancient grounds and architecture stands in stark contrast to the skyscrapers still visible from most of the garden. Most of Tokyo is like this, wide streets filled with technology, bustling with people and shopowners yelling about what you can buy at their store (I think), and the next street will be nothing more than an alleyway, quiet, with clothes hanging to dry on the balcony, the houses muted colors with curved roofs made of wood. The gardens are beautiful and Miranda and I mostly wandered and talked. Although we’ve seen each other every year since we were 14, this is our first time we’ve really travelled somewhere together. I’ve found that our lack of planning and “go with the flow” attitude has actually made us great travel companions. After the imperial palace, we spent some time wandering through Tokyo Station and then hit probably the only ramen place I’ll be able to eat at on this trip. The vegan and halal ramen shop in Shinjuku, called Ouka, employs mostly women and is overrun by foreigners. It had a bit of a wait, but it was well worth it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/9dgc4LQm.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Imperial Palace&quot; /&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/rbTcQSvm.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Swans Near Tokyo Station&quot; /&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/8snRRoFm.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Vegan Ramen&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 10 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/articles/2018-03/Harajuku-and-the-Imperial-Palace</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/articles/2018-03/Harajuku-and-the-Imperial-Palace</guid>
        
        
        <category>Japan</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Tama and Family</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;One uber, two bus rides and and an 11 hour flight later, I finally made it to my family’s place in Tama. I’ll be staying in my Great Uncle’s apartment, just a floor away from his daughter and grandchildren. Uncle Mori moved back to Japan last year after living in the United States for 40 years. He tells me that this is not the Japan he once lived in, technology so embedded in everything he struggles just with the washing machine. I’m excited to see him and spend time with him, I’ve always felt like he and my great aunt (my grandma’s sister) were like another pair of grandparents. After my grandma passed, Aunt Kumiko kept me in touch with my Japanese side. Their grandchildren would come to visit and they became like cousins to me. There was always a language barrier to overcome but we bonded over Powderpuff Girls and communicated through hand signals. As we grew older, I was able to take them with me around Los Angeles.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With them, I feel comfortable; I stayed in this apartment the last time I was here with my Mom and my “Aunt” Keiko and Uncle Mori are both fluent in English. When I wander outside of the apartment though, I feel out of place. At 5’7”, I’m taller than most girls here and a lot of the guys. My family lives in a suburb of Tokyo and I haven’t seen a single foreigner anywhere near here. As I leave my Uncle’s apartment I hear a little asking her mom who I am. I keep forgetting to speak Japanese, and respond in English or give up on a sentence halfway through. There was a time when I seriously considered moving to Japan to teach English, but after spending a week here with my mother I felt too rude and restricted to ever live here.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/DE0HOV3m.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Korochan&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today it rained all day, something that Los Angeles has been lacking this winter. I split the day with spending time with my cousin and uncle, and trying to finish homework before Miranda arrives. I got lost trying to find a cafe in Shibuya called Caffice . It’s filled with other people working, and I even see a guy with a Randy’s Donuts sticker on his laptop. The wifi is fast, but the coffee is expensive ($8 for a mocha!). Although I liked the workspace vibe, I’d probably find a cheaper place to work if I planned on staying more than a couple of hours.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/Rnwpy2qm.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;KoheiAndMori&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Miranda’s bus arrived 40 minutes late most likely due to rain. My uncle, always accommadating, braved the cold and waited with me. After 30 hours of travelling, Miranda is ready to call it night and my jetlag catches up to me as well.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 08 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/articles/2018-03/Tama-and-Family</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/articles/2018-03/Tama-and-Family</guid>
        
        
        <category>Japan</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A Packing List, Everything Plus the Kitchen Sink</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The past few weeks have been a blur of running errands, making never ending lists, and trying to focus on school work. Preparing for this trip has been a little crazy as I’ve tried to balance having to carry a full set of camping gear along with clothes to keep me cozy through a chilly Japanese spring, fall in New Zealand, and a sunny Hawaii in April. In case anybody’s curious here’s everything I brought along (I am well aware I am bringning too many clothes).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/CevJ8LGl.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Packing&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;clothes&quot;&gt;Clothes&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Sandals, flats, and hiking boots&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;(6) T-shirts&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;(4) Long sleeves&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;(4) Tank tops&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;(2) Spaghetti straps&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;(3) Work out shirts&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;(2) Top and bottom thermals&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;(2) Leggings&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;(2) Jeans&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Tights&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Jean, work out, and pajama shorts&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Flannel&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Hoodie&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Fleece jacket&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Rain jacket&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Dress&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;(2) Gloves&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;(2) Headbands&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Beanie&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Scarf&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;camping-gear&quot;&gt;Camping Gear&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Tent&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Sleeping bag and pad&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Multitool and pocket knmife&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Jet boiler&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Pan&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Folding spatula&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Spork&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Insect net&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Sink&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Biodegradable soap&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Sponge&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Clips and rope (for laundry)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;electronics&quot;&gt;Electronics&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Headlamp&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Lantern&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Reading light&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Extra batteries&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;(2) External batteries&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Car charger&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;AUX cord&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Laptop and laptop charger&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Camera, extra batteries, and chargers&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Headphones and bluetooth headphones&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Fujifilm camera&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Attachable phone lens’&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;miscellaneous&quot;&gt;Miscellaneous&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Umbrella&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Reusable Bag&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Small purse&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Sunglasses&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Teddy bear&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Water bottle&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;toiletries&quot;&gt;Toiletries&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Toiletries are a pretty personal choice, so I don’t feel like anyone would gain anything from me posting mine&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 06 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/articles/2018-03/a-packing-list</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/articles/2018-03/a-packing-list</guid>
        
        
        <category>Packing</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
